<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Welcome</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 13:38:27 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Research&#34;</title>
      <link>/posts/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 13:38:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/research/</guid>
      <description>Hi, this is my actual first post, although the title might say &amp;#34;my second post&amp;#34;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-me/</guid>
      <description>CV / Github / Google Scholar
I am an Assistant Professor in the Department of Statistics at the University of California, Santa Cruz. Before my current position, I was a post-doctoral researcher (advised by Jacob Bien), with a PhD from Carnegie Mellon University (advised by Max G&amp;#39;Sell and Ryan Tibshirani).
My research interests include oceanographic data analysis, epidemiological modeling/forecasting, changepoint detection, and selective inference. More generally, I develop statistical tools for large complex data in real-world scientific applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Ocean data analysis Ocean Mover’s Distance: Using Optimal Transport for Analyzing Oceanographic Data Sangwon Hyun, Aditya Mishra, Christopher L. Follett Bror Jonsson, Gemma Kulk, Gael Forget, Marie-Fanny Racault, Thomas Jackson, Stephanie Dutkiewic, Christian L. Müller, and Jacob Bien Proceedings of the Royal Society A (2022)
Density-based Approaches to Evaluate Biogeochemical Models by Satellite Derived Chlorophyll Bror F. Jönsson, Christopher L. Follett, Jacob Bien, Stephanie Dutkiewicz, Sangwon Hyun, Gemma Kulk, Gael Forget, Christian L.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
